JON YEATMAN

jonlyeatman@gmail.com | 404-423-7274 | https://www.jonyeatman.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/jon-yeatman

SUMMARY

Thorough and meticulous **Business Analyst/Administrator** passionate about helping businesses succeed. Former **small business owner** and certified **full-stack web developer**. Organized problem solver with a strong technical aptitude and ability to partner with leadership, sales, marketing, support and other important teams to maximize operations and interactions. Experience with various stages of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) especially design, analysis, deployment and maintenance.

EXPERIENCE

Honu Management Group

Coordinator, Nov 2021 - Present

- Created an interactive dashboard and corresponding reports to improve workflow and manual documenting of inventory information
- Ensured staff is properly trained
- Analyzed operation processes to create and maintain efficiencies

Phoenix Custom Printing, LLC

Founder & Director of Operations, 2018 - Present

- Oversaw the competitive bid and negotiation process with vendors and suppliers
- Maximized immediate turn-around by minimizing unnecessary overhead
- Partnered with local third-party vendors to create a streamline process for clients
- Quality relationship building with clients for trustworthy product delivery

Lead Graphic Designer

Superior Edge Leather Works, LLC, 2017 - 2019

- Consistently delivered close to 500 designs quarterly per clientele
- Optimized processes working with a variety of garments, inks and merchandise
- Streamlined production pipeline for multi-faceted items

Michgan Army National Guard

Infantryman, 2013 - 2017

- Displayed a high-level of competence and professionalism under stressful situations
- Supervised, trained and ensured the safety and welfare of a 4-person team, maintaining a 100% safety record

EDUCATION

Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI

Certificate, Full-Stack Development, 2021

OTHER

Technical Skills: Microsoft Office, Salesforce, Relational Databases (MySQL), Tableau, SharePoint and advanced Microsoft Excel functions, Programming languages (Python, React, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery)

Strengths: Leadership, Project Management, Training and Instructing, Out-of-the-Box Thinking,

Business-Strategy, Attention to Detail, Efficiency, Data Analysis